are you afraid of
ты боишься
Kadyrov I don't know
Кадырова Я не знаю
Kadyrov immediately lost
Кадырова сразу пропало
knowledge Hello Hello Where are you
знание Привет Здравствуйте Ты
from
откуда
m the Republic of
м республика
Buryatia myself a Buryat Mongol who is a Buryat understood I
Бурятия сам бурят Монгол кто бурят понял
wonder what the movie is about in general
интересно о чём вобще
movie series Listen how do you
кино кино сериалы Слушай как ты
rate the fact that during the Soviet
оцениваешь то что во время Советского
Union a lot of
Союза было уничтожено очень много
Buryat intelligentsia was destroyed they closed
бурятской интеллигенции закрывали
[music]
[музыка]
datsans What do you know about this I'm
дацаны Что вы об этом знаете я вот тебя
asking you No well I could
спрашиваю Не ну я мог бы
ask some Tola
какие-то меня спрашивают Тола
struggle here we can have
борьба вот у нас понятия могут быть
different concepts I That's why I asked in advance What
разные я Поэтому заранее спросил Что вы
else do you know about this struggle of whom was going on with whom
об этом ещё знаете борьба кого с кем шла
Well the struggle was that there was those who
Ну борьба была то что была те кто
adhered to the Soviet idea those who
придерживается Советской идеи те кто
believed that pan-Mongolism was cool Yeah,
считал что панмонголизм - это круто Угу
got it And what ideas are you a follower of that are
понял А вы приверженец каких
closer to me Marxist ideas you are a
идей мне ближе марксистские идеи вы
Marxist
марксист
Well Marx and I read closer I said that I
Ну Маркс и читал ближе Я сказал что я не
can't say for myself as a Marxist I
могу себе сказать как марксист я
suppose not
допустим не
everything that's maximum not everything observing
всё вот вот максимально не всё соблюдая
maybe some moments And what do
может быть какие-то моменты А что
you observe that you don't observe from
соблюдаешь что не соблюдаешь из
Marxism
марксизма
Well well I'm not a member of the
Ну ну я не состою в
party That's exactly more precisely you can't
партии Вот именно точнее ты не можешь
because because there is no Marxist
потому что потому что нету марксистской
party you have no party in Russia there is no
партии у вас в России нету партии
party at all parties How exactly which
вообще партии Как именно который
is in the State Duma is not in the State Duma
находится в госдуме нет в госдуме все
they are all more or less controlled Well there are
они контролируются более-менее Ну есть
some guys who are there
некоторые ребята которые являются там
approximately at least I know at least four
примерно хотя бы я как минимум четверых
who Mark read
знаю кто Марк со читал
and I understand that they at least understand
и и понимаю что они как минимум понимают
what an
что такое
idea is I understood And what is a Marxist idea for you
идея понял А в чём для тебя Марксистская
Well Marx believed that
идея Ну Маркс считал что
firstly that here it is necessary to engage in science
во-первых что тут надо заниматься наукой
that science It will help a person to increase
что наука Она поможет человеку повысить
labor productivity and by increasing
производительность труда а повысив
labor productivity a person
труда человек
will receive by freeing himself a little well by
получит освободив как бы себя немножко
raising
ну подняв
productivity Benefit free
производительность Выгода свободное
time for development for the comprehensive
время для развития для всестороннего
development of a person roughly speaking so and then
развития человека грубо говоря так а то
you do not agree with this No, I do not I do
ты с этим не согласен Да не я Я
not I agree with this You asked
не я с этим согласен Вот вы спросили
me about Marxism and for some reason you
меня о марксизме и вот вы почему-то
asked why I do not agree with this I do
спросили почему я с этим не согласен Я
not know I know that they it That's exactly how it is
не знаю я знаю что они оно Именно так
written No there are details further I read
написано Нет там детали дальше я читал
there more specific how do you evaluate the
там более конкретные как ты оцениваешь
modern state of the Russian
современное государство Российской
Federation as an Empire as a
Федерации как Империю как что
capitalist capitalist
капиталистическая капиталистическая
country maybe we
страна может быть мы сейчас
are now as it is in an imperialist
находимся как его в империалистической
time we live when all other
время живём когда все остальные
states  and Russia, among other things,
государства и России в том числе
are imperialist
являются империалистическими
powers. Yeah, I got it. Well, again, an
державами Угу понял Ну опять
imperialist power is, according to
империалистическая держава - это по по
Lenin's term. Don't you think that Russia
Ленина Тебе не кажется что Россия
is at
находится на
the level of feudalism and not
уровне феодализма а не
capitalism,
капитализма
first of all? No, it doesn't seem so. It's just that the
во-первых Нет не кажется про просто
level of feudalism also needs to be
уровень феодализма тоже надо дать
defined. You can probably give the level. You
определение Вот вы можете наверное дать
call it the time of capitalism. There are
называете вре капитализма есть
capitalists, but who is a capitalist? No, it's not
капиталисты да кто капиталист Нет не
necessary. How is capitalism without
обязательно как это капитализм без
capitalists? Well, look. Who is this layer?
капиталистов Ну смотрите Кто этот слой
Which layer? Bourgeois. Who is he in Russia,
который слой Буржуа Кто он в России
for example? Don't look. I'll say the following.
пример Не смотрите вот я скажу следующее
But still, time is not simply determined
А всё-таки время определяется не просто
in one country. There is
в одной стране там является
in one country. Let's say, if we
в одной стране там вот допустим Если мы
take the 10th century. China. China and Great
берём там X век Китай Китай и
Britain. You call them
Великобритания вы там называете там
[music] there.
[музыка]
Eh, China was a
э Китай
monarchical state. Yes, yes, a
типа монархическим государствам да да
feudal state. Then there
феодальным государством тогда очень
were a lot of provinces there. Yes, they have
много там было провинций Да они более
lower labor productivity. But when it is
низкий производительность труда но когда
considered. So,
считается Так
capital is lower, let's say, a
капита более низший более скажем так
lower socio-economic structure.
низкий социально-экономический уклад
Economic structure. It is considered
хозяйственный уклад он считается
that, well, well, yes, it is in a
что ну каком-то ну да он находится в
losing state, but for the whole
проигрышем состоянии но для для всего
world.  proletariat and other
мирового пролетариата и других
states it is considered that we
государств считается что мы всё-таки
are still in a capitalist time and Yes
находимся в капиталистическое время и Да
if one state stands out then we need to
если одно государство выделяется то надо
look at the nature of the labor
смотреть по характеру проводите труда
and also
и а также
by
по по
these by the form of ownership by the form of
этим по форме собственности по форме
ownership We have a lot of
собственности У нас очень много
capitalists
капиталистов
Now let's go you've spoken two pages of
Теперь давай ты наговорил страницы две
text So let's go again Give
текста Так давай теперь ещё раз Назови
me an example of capitalists in Russia who are these
мне пример капиталистов в России кто эти
bourgeois e u va capitalism who is a
буржу е у ва капитализм кто
capitalist Gotha
капиталист Гота
who owns there Miller is the head of
кто обладает там Миллер глава
this not Miller is the head of Gazprom he is not a
этого не Миллер глава Газпрома он не
capitalist he does not own Gazprom but
капиталист ему не принадлежит Газпром но
it turns out he is a capitalist these are those he is
он получается капиталист это те он
simply not a miller just a pound put to
просто не милер просто поставленный фунт
manage this all he is these are capitalists yes these are those
управлять этим всё он это капиталисты да
who are bourgeois who
это те которые Буржуа которые
have private ownership of the means of
имеют частную собственность на средства
production on a huge scale
производства в огромных масштабах
who is a capitalist who is a
кто капиталист кто
capitalist Well I have already explained to you that
капиталист Ну я вам объяснил уже что
then Who else could
потом Кто ещё может
be
быть
Usmanov billionaire who owns mail.ru then
Усманов миллиардер владеющий mail.ru
Look who is the ruling class during
Смотри кто есть правящим классом во
capitalism under the ruling
капитализма при правящим
class the ruling class
классом правящим классом
can be in principle any class except except the
может быть в принципе любой класс кроме
proletariat again Who is the ruling
пролетариата ещё раз Кто есть правящий
class under capitalism Well look if
класс при капитализме Ну смотрите если
you open the book class war in
вы откроете книгу классовая война во
France it says
Франции то там говорится
that  there you can see that there were
что там можно заметить что там был
several groups of capitalists
несколько групп капиталистов
let's look there is for example the
давай смотри есть например класс
aristocracy class Yes there is a class of Bourgeois
аристократия Да вот есть класс Буржуа
capitalists Yes there is a working class Yes
капиталисты Да есть класс рабочий Да
there are declassed elements marginals
есть деклассированные элементы маргиналы
Yes during communism yes to whom to whom who
Да во время коммунизма да кому кому кто
is the ruling
есть правящим
class in communism and classless
классом в коммунизме и бес классовое
society Okay under socialism
общество Окей при социализме
who Well the Working Class which
кто Ну Рабочий Класс который
tries the proletariat yes in a feudal
пытается пролетариат да в феодальном
society who is the ruling
обществе кто господствующий
class feudal lords can be aristocracy Yes
класс феодалы могут быть аристократия Да
aristocracy aristocracy or not always
аристократия аристократия или не всегда
yes this is feudal lords and there were
да это же есть Феодалы и были
aristocrats yes this is a stratum Yes
аристократи да это это прослойка Да
now during capitalism Who is the
теперь во время капитализма Кто есть
ruling
правящим
class can fight industrial
классом могут бороться промышленные
capitals financial capitalists
капитали финансовыми капиталистами
capitalists Which it doesn't matter capitalists yes that
капиталисты Какие неважно капиталисты да
is
то есть во
during this as it is
время этого как оно
capitalism capitalists are the ruling
капитализма капиталисты есть правящим
class they essentially determine policy
классом они по сути определяют политику
they appoint the head of state and
они ставят руководителя государства и
so on Yes come on Putin in the
так дальше Да давай так Путин в
modern Russian Federation is a
современном Российской Федерации есть
protg of capital
ставленника капитала
to a certain extent Yes
в определённой степени Да
no capital does not control Putin it
нет капитал не управляет Путиным он
controls the capitalists
управляет капиталистами
so for example
так вот например
he wanted and from this owner of
захотел он и у этого у собственников
Domodedovo the airport was taken away
Домодедова отжали аэропорт
everything court  decided and
всё суд постановил и
everything is actually a repression organ
всё является собственно репрессий орган
yes yes that is it turns out Look not
да да то есть получается Смотри не
capitalists not capitalists there is a
капиталисты не капиталисты тут есть
ruling class here but some other subjects
правящий класс а некто другие субъекты
Who are
Кто
they
они
well you know I will tell you that Napoleon II
ну знаете я вам скажу что Наполеон II
came to power
пришёл это во власть потому
because Napoleon T Yes Peter I I want to say
что Наполеон Т Да Пётр I Я хочу сказать
No I want to say when when he
Нет я хочу сказать когда когда он к
came to power they fought Well he convinced the
ласти пришёл они боролись Ну он убедил
population that they are fighting against
население что они борются против
come on so who makes the decision in Russia
давай так кто в России принимает решение
and against Who makes the
и против Кто в России принимает
decision in Russia Who in Russia are the security forces security
решение Кто в России силовики силовой
agency who security agency
орган кто силовой орган
appoints Well who is the head of the entire security
назначает Ну кто глава всего силового
agency at the moment is Putin the
органа на данный момент является Путин
commander-in-chief who
главнокомандующий кто Путина
appoints Putin appoints Well it goes through a
назначает назначает Ну проходит это
democratic process
демократическим условно процессом
conditionally Putin
условно Путина
appoints capital
назначает капитал
no What capital does he appoint
нет Какой капитал он назначает
Putin appoints who
Путина назначает кто
[music]
[музыка]
Putin capital no no well why look
Путин капитал нет нет ну почему смотрите
firstly firstly resources resources
во-первых во-первых ресурсы ресурсы
are located Well
находятся Ну вот
this is
это
concentrated me again again
концентрированное мене ещё раз ещё раз
look not this
смотри не это
uh not capital you change the president yes
ээ не капитал у вас меняет президента да
Or for example you have Putin is actually the
Или например у вас Путин есть фактически
sole
единоличным
ruler and he
правителем и он себя
elects himself Well you agree that elections
избирает Ну ты согласись что выборы у
you don't have democratic elections
вас демократических выборов у вас нет у
you have a
вас
fiction democratic elections
фикция демократические выборы
are present only depending on the
присутствуют только в зависимости от
importance of the
важности
decision I don't understand what does depending on the
решения Что значит в зависимости от
importance of the decision mean you
важности решения не понял
can define Well at the local level
можно определить Ну на местных уровнях у
we can have democracy Dava we're
нас может существовать демократи Дава мы
not talking about local Dava we're
сейчас не про мест Дава мы сейчас про
talking about presidential elections now
выборы президента мы с тобой говорим нет
we're talking about all elections about
Ну мы же говорим про про все выборы про
everything No let's start with
все Нет давай сначала мы про выборы
presidential elections look Well presidential elections are the
президента смотрите Ну выборы президента
most important
- это самая жи это самая большая
position let's do it Do you have
должность давай так у вас У вас есть
democratic elections of the president or not a
демократические выборы президента или не
fiction
фикция
Well the last time it was in 1996
Ну вот В девяносто шестом последний раз
I don't know here In 1996 there
было я не знаю вот В девяносто шестом
were pos That is, now there are none yes that is,
были пос То есть сейчас нету да то есть
in fact Putin appoints himself
по сути Путин сам себя назначает сам
extends his powers through
продлевает себе полномочия через типа
fictitious elections
фиктивные выборы
so
так
legitimization is not a reform as it is well
легитимизации не реформа как его ну
amendments to the Constitution
внесение поправок в Конституцию пра
right amendments were made and it
правки и
turns out new rules came where is he
получается новые правила пришли где он
Again again Yes again He decides who
Заново заново Да заново Он решает ккто
will run who will die in prison
будет баллотироваться кто умрёт в тюрьме
like Navalny Yes and who will be elected as he is again
как Навальный Да а кого как его снова
Well you agree yes then  there are the
выберут Ну ты согласись да то есть
last elections you said yourself you
последние выборы ты же сам сказал у вас
had them in deno sixth year Well, the last
были в дено шестом году Да ну последние
presidential elections are honest Yes,
выборы президента президента честны Да
we are all other elections
мы все остальные выборы
and the thing is that look who will
а дело в том что смотри кого кого кого
be put in charge of whom there in your city
вам там поставят там э в вашем городе
in general in Russia no one cares
вообще в России никого не интересует
Because there is a power Vertical
Потому что есть силовая Вертикаль
that will talk and will do
которая ээ будет говорить и будут делать
everything that it says and that's all that is we
всё что она скажет вот и всё то есть мы
saw that in your country it is not
посмотрели что у вас не
capital that brings the president Yes, like in a
капитал приводит президента Да как в
bourgeois society Yes, for example, if
буржуазном обществе Да вот например если
we look at the
мы посмотрим
US we can say that capital yes we
ээ США можно сказать что капитал да мы
see there is a capitalist Elon Musk Yes, he is a
видим там капиталист илон Маск Да он
capitalist capitalist Buzha Yes, others There are
капиталист капиталист бужа Да другие Там
gunsmiths and so on that is
оружейники и так дальше то есть
Republicans they are a lot of
республиканцы они очень много
leading Republicans they
ээ ведущих республиканцев они
are big Bourgeois there we can say that
ээ крупные Буржуа там можно сказать что
there is capitalism in Russia there is no capitalism in Russia all
там капитализм в России нет в России все
these big Bourgeois so to speak Yes, they
эти крупные Буржуа так сказать Да они
all go under Putin's Nogotkov and he
все ходят под Ноготков у Путина и он
will want to reset any of them with one button the
захочет одной кнопкой обнулить любого из
Armed Forces That is it turns out that Russia is in
ВС То есть получается Россия находится в
I would say a feudal society where
я бы сказал феодальном обществе где
there is an
есть
emperor and his vassals like there
император есть его вассалы типа там
Ramzan Kadyrov Here he has
Рамзан Кадыров Вот у него есть Вотчина
his patrimony  Chechnya
его Чечня его
put him there he does what he wants Yes, that's
надел он там делает что хочет Да есть
it, he has to
вот он должен
serve
служить
Wednesday, that's
сре
it, Ramzan Kadyrov can do
есть Рамзан Кадыров может сделать с
whatever he wants to you, nothing will happen to him for it,
тобой что угодно ему за это ничего не
really
правда
M, not quite So, what will happen to him? Well,
М не совсем Так а что ему будет Ну
first of all, if it turns out that each of
во-первых если у Если получается каждое
his decisions still requires a
его решение всё-таки требует
certain amount of money, for
определённых изменя денег средств не
example, let's say if Ramzan Kadyrov
например скажем так если Рамзан Кадыров
wants to break your jaw and breaks
захочет сломать тебе челюсть и сломает
your jaw and writes about it on his
челюсть и напишет об этом у себя в
Instagram, he will get something for it. Let me be
Инстаграме ему будет за это что-то Дай
honest, I think, what
почесна думаю да что
will happen? Well, first of all, if Ramzan Kadyrov
будет Ну во-первых если Рамзан Кадыров
officially breaks someone's forehead, it
сво официально кому-то чель сломает это
will be a big scandal, it will be like a mini
будет большой скандал это как мини ему
scandal for him, you will cry,
будет скандал вы будете плакать там
your friends will write there on Telegram,
будут твои друзья писать там в телеграме
what will happen,
е что что будет
he will suffer losses,
ему понесёт онные потери
what kind of cyn Why would he break someone's
какую цины Зачем ему кому-то ломать
jaw? What kind of reputation does he have, on the contrary,
челюсть Какая репутация у него наоборот
for him, reputation is cool, he is a cool
для него репутация это круто он крутой
Alpha male and that's it. He does what he wants,
Альфа самец и всё Он что хочет и делат
look, you saw the situation when
смотри ты же видел э ситуацию когда ээ
he brought his son to the pre-trial detention center
он привёл своего сына в СИЗО
fifteen year old son and he beat a
пятнадцатилетнего сына да и он бил
Russian guy on camera and he also
русского парня на камеру и он ещё
posted it on Instagram what happened to him for
Выложил это в Instagram что ему было за
it Well, what did they look at him that the
это Ну что на него посмотрели что
man acted very unworthily Vova
человек очень недостойно поступил Вовы
gave an order to a small one how much crowbar
дали дали орден малому сколько лому
after that three or four orders were given
после этого три или четыре ордена дали
from different republics Well, yes, most of
от разных респуб Ну бо да большинство
those who obey and can
тех кто подчиняется и может ему
give him medals in principle, you can just medals
дать принципе медали можно просто медали
but a lot can in principle reach
ено множество можно в принципе дойти
finish North Korea Yes, how did
закончить Северной Корее Да как как
Ramzan Kadyrov and his son suffer punishment
понёс наказание Рамзан Кадыров и его
reputation what kind of reputation
сын репутационный како репутационный
Well, some Yes, we are not talking about
Ну некоторые Да так мы же говорим не про
reputation But about the law, that is, he
репутацию А про закон то есть его там
should have been held accountable There is
должны были привлечь к ответственно Есть
legislation of the Russian Federation Yes,
законодательство Российской Федерации Да
if he is not some kind of aristocracy that is
если он не есть какой-то аристократия
above the law, the process is going on
которая выше закона процесс идёт
at certain certain questions there
у определённые определённые вопросы там
were scandals In power, what kind of process stop
скандалы были Во власти какой проце стоп
again look Ramzan Kadyrov publicly applied his
ещ раз смотри Рамзан Кадыров прил своего
son to his knees, he is
сына публично он коленями
simply imprisoned, not to mention a
просто заключён не то что заключённого
prisoner from a pre-trial detention center Yes, he broke it off so in short
человека из СИЗО Да отломал так короче
on camera and he also posted it publicly
на камеру и он ещё Выложил это публично
these bullying posted on his page
эти издевательства выложил у себя в
Instagram Yes and say like this Skim him for
Инстаграме Да и ска вот так Ским ему за
this absolutely nothing it is a
это ничего абсолютно это
real crime According to the Criminal
реально преступление Согласно Уголовного
Code of the Russian Federation causing
кодекса Российской Федерации нанесение
bodily harm
телесных увечий
Yes abuse of power And so on
Да злоупотребление властью И так дальше
and a bunch of other things there Yes neither he nor his offspring did
и куча всего там да ни онни его отпрыск
not bear any
не понёс никакого
punishment Pons, it seems, no, I
наказания понс вроде как нет я же
explained No Well from the Ukrainian point of view
объяснил Нет ну с украинской точки может
maybe so we say Look I am a person with a
быть и так мы говорим Смотри я человек с
legal education there is a concept of
юридическим образованием есть понятие
legal responsibility Yes he is there even
юридическая ответственность Да его там
either to administrative or
даж либо к административке либо к
criminal Yes What is this
уголовке да В чём это ответственность
responsibility no responsibility No
никакой ответственности Нет
reputational it is you just began to
репутационное это ты просто стал его
consider him more of an [ __ ] than you thought before to
считать больше мудаком чем считал раньше
him for this He and you like that and you
ему на это Он и тебя так и просто ты
will simply treat him even worse his
будешь ээ ещё хуже к нему относиться его
reputation in your eyes will fall And he will give
репутация в твоих глазах упадёт А он
you another
тебе ещё
dressing down Well it's the same as if one person
разнос Ну это всё равно что человек один
one person said that he came for one
один человек сказал что пришёл на один
term And remained in fact Well about more than
срок А остался по сути Ну про больше
his term is now In power
своего срока сейчас находится Во власти
in about the same situation
в примерно так такое же положение
as far as I
насколько я
understand there He somehow said something that
понимаю там Он как-то что-то сказал что
he could then this person,
его можно будет потом этого человека
uh, as if to
ээ как бы
kick him out of office but somehow it didn't
выгнать с должности но как-то не
work out  let's say this if Ramzan
получилось скажем так если Рамзан
Kadyrov wants you to apologize on
Кадыров захочет чтобы ты извинился на
camera you will most likely apologize
камеру ты скорее всего извинишься
No, you are quite
нет ты довольно
brave And what what with what should I
смелый А что что с чем мне
apologize with what to apologize for Honestly they
извиняться с чем извинятся Вот честно
say there is power in Truth
говорят сила в Правде че
Well, for example, Ramzan Kadyrov
Ну вот например Рамзану Кадырову не
will not like what you said, that he suffered
понравится что ты сказал что он понёс
reputational losses, so he thinks that
репутационные потери вот он считает что
this is slander and will say the World Cup KTA Well, I don't know,
это клевета и скажет ЧМ КТА Ну не знаю
he won't like the tone in which
вот ему там не понравится тон в котором
you spoke and specially
ты говорил да и приедут специально
trained people will come from Chechnya And they will tell you
обученные люди из Чечни Да и скажут тебе
Ramzan Kadyrov is a good person, you need to
Рамзан кадырович хороший человек надо
apologize, we beg you, how are
извиниться очень тебя просим как ты Ну
you Well, if if he stoops to his this is this is like this, I don't know Zelensky can afford to pay attention to everyone to each person that they will say something bad about him I think that what if a person stoops to this But this is just some kind of clinic But I
Но это прям совсем какая-то клиника Но я
think that a person Nako nepu in front of
считаю что человек Нако непу перед
Ramzan Karo And why apologize Well, if
рамзаном Каро А зачем извиняться Ну если
he stoops and people from him come
вот он опустится и приедут от него люди
and say  look he went down so that you
и скажут смотри он опустился чтобы ты
changed your ways to apologize sometimes sometimes I
что извиняться изменился иногда иногда
don't know some decisions it's
каких-то решений не
not
знаю не
worth it sometimes it's not worth it because
стоит иногда не стоит потому что потому
because I didn't do anything special in front of the person
что я перед человеком Ничего особенного
first of all
не сделал это вопервых
he well why should I start You again you
он ну зачем м пускаться Вы опять же вы
again are trying to build yourself up there swear
опять же пытаетесь там строите себя мат
Well only Zelensky can allow this
Ну такой позволить может только
I consider him as if Zelensky
Зеленский Я считаю его как бы Зеленским
if something like this happens But this is
если вот такое получится Но это
Zelensky
Зеленский
I don't know
же я не знаю
Kadyrov immediately lost
Кадырова сразу пропало
knowledge I don't know Kadyrov what do I need I do
знание Я не знаю Кадырова че мне бото Я
n't
же не
know some kind of big threat that's
знаю какая-то угроза большая я вот
why I'm saying some kind of
поэтому и говорю какие-то
messages
сообщения
This is a bomb
какие Это бомба
switched like squeak ko it was
переключил лайк писка ко было
divine yes
божественно да
letter on y Instagram I don't know why
пись на й Instagram Я не знаю для чого
this is for you to watch on your face and for
це то для тоб там дивитись на оце а для
you one two or three clicks But you are watching
теце оди два або три клика Але ты тримае
me and I will be like in me there are a bunch of fouls
мене и я буду каза в мене там Купа фолов
and in me there will be a cool mood to do
и в мене буде класний настр щоб робити
but cool video letter on y Instagram while Ai
но крут вдео пись на й Instagram пок Ай
Here  Come on, I'm waiting for you
Вот давай я тея чекаю